NURHAMSAH

Fullstack Developer Indonesia, Jawa Timur, Kediri, Mojo 64162 0812-1322-1343 https://nurhamsah.vercel.app/

SUMMARY

a professional software developer and has quite a lot of experience building projects with a great team. Very proficient in using the React / Next js framework and always prioritizes code performance, security and user experience to achieve amazing results.

EDUCATION

SMK PGRI KRAS - Kediri, Indonesia (2014 - 2017)

Computer and network engineer

PERSONAL PROJECT

Mini Restaurant App

https://github.com/nurhamsah1998/Restaurant

Bertanya App

https://bertanya.vercel.app/

Todo Premium App

https://todo-premium.vercel.app/

CERTIFICATE

Laravel Web Development (May 02 - Jun 23, 2023)

PKS Digital School

No. 6162/PKS/DigiS/VI/2023

https://member.pksdigitalschool.id/sertifikat/generate/b66f9455-9ef5-4020-928b-6e18923a8470

SKILLS

- · HTML, CSS, SCSS
- · JavaScript, TypeScript
- PHP
- Git
- Figma
- · Github, Gitlab
- React JS
- Next JS
- React Native
- Laravel
- · Redux, Jotai, Zustand
- Jest, Cypress
- REST API
- Node JS
- Firebase
- Supabase
- · Sequelize
- Prisma
- Express
- Nest JS
- · Postgre, Mysql

WORK EXPERIENCE

Al Monitoring - Jawa barat, Indonesia

Fullstack developer (Jul 2024 - present)

Freelance - Remote

- · User authentication 2 role
- UI/UX design
- · Making reusable component
- Managing webhook
- · Dashboard analytic Al agent
- · Customize HTML embedding
- · Responsive & dark mode & light mode
- · Integration options

Photo Printing - Jawa timur, Indonesia

Frontend developer (May 2024 - Aug 2024)

Freelance - Remote

- · Dashboard analytic
- CRUD
- · Read swagger API documentation
- Fixing bug

Feedloop - Jawa barat, Indonesia

Frontend developer (Apr 2023 - Apr 2024)

Fulltime - Remote

- · Integration unit test using Jest / React testing library
- · Debugging Create advanced features
- · Daily / weekly meeting
- · Convert figma to code
- · Team work

School Web App - Jawa timur, Indonesia

Fullstack developer (Nov 2022 - Nov 2023)

Freelance - Remote

- · Create dynamic student bills
- · Announcement management
- · Role management
- · Security authentication
- · Management student (Grade, Bill report, Account, ect.)

Code Art Online - Jawa timur, Indonesia

Frontend developer (Dec 2021 - Feb 2023)

Fulltime - Onsite

- · Integration unit test using cypress
- · Working on various application features from clients
- · Convert figma to code
- · Improvment feature cashier mobile app
- · Weekly meeting
- · Team work